pentaximaging.com 2017-09-29

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting ricoh-imaging.com, the Web site of RICOH IMAGING AMERICAS CORPORATION At ricoh-imaging.com, we respect your privacy. This page will give you an overview of our privacy policy, what information we collect when you visit our site and how that information is used, how you can contact us to be removed from a mailing list to which you have subscribed, and a general disclaimer about the use of the content on our site. If you have any questions that are not answered here, please don't hesitate to ask us directly.

### General information we gather

Whenever you visit ricoh-imaging.com we gather general information about your visit - the site you are coming from, pages or areas you visit on our site, and how long you stay at a particular location on the site. This information helps us identify popular areas of our site as well as areas that could use refinement, so that we can keep content on the site fresh and relevant to our users' interests. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on this data. We do not collect any personally identifiable information from you except when you expressly volunteer it under special circumstances described below, such as entering a contest.

### Are Cookies used?

Yes, but only to collect the aforementioned information. In addition we also use Google Analytics service to measure traffic, and anonymous visitor behavior. To accomplish this, Google Analytics employs the use of anonymous persistent cookies. Cookies are text files that are saved by your browser (e.g., Internet Explorer) and stored on your computer's hard drive. They do not pose any threat to your computer. As stated above, these cookies do not identify, monitor, or track any personally identifiable information. To find out more about how this information is used or to read the Google Analytics privacy policy, go to https://www.google.com/privacy.html.

Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies without asking the user if he/she wants to do so, but you can usually change your browser to notify you when there is a cookie so you can choose whether to accept or decline the cookie. If you choose to decline one of our cookies, you will still be able to use the features on our site.

### We gather personal data ONLY at your request

If at some point during your visit to ricoh-imaging.com you take part in a contest or promotion, order brochures, download documents or other software, or if you choose to contact us for some reason, we may ask for personal information such as your name, address, and e-mail address. We also may ask you for information about your interests, opinions and background so that we can better interact with you in the future and better understand your needs as a customer. Providing such information is always optional on your part.

### How to be removed from our mailing list after you've subscribed

When you submit personal information to us, you also may choose to be notified by e-mail about additional products and services offered by RICOH IMAGING AMERICAS CORPORATION If at any time after signing up for our mailing list you would prefer to be removed from it, you can always send a message to [support@ricoh-imaging.com](mailto:support@ricoh-imaging.ca?Subject=Ricoh%20Support%20Claim) and ask to be taken off our list. Or, you can simply reply to an e-mail from us and type REMOVE in the subject line.

### Disclosure policy

Information collected at ricoh-imaging.com will not be sold, rented, lent or otherwise disclosed to anyone other than to RICOH IMAGING AMERICAS CORPORATION's retailers (for purposes of a product sale initiated by the customer), RICOH IMAGING AMERICAS CORPORATION's affiliated companies - which include RICOH IMAGING COMPANY LTD. (RICOH IMAGING AMERICAS CORPORATION's parent company) - and direct and indirect subsidiaries of RICOH IMAGING AMERICAS CORPORATION Any personal information you may choose to give us is used only to fulfill the service you have requested, such as ordering a document or subscribing to a mailing list.
